德古拉  前情提要
Previously, on Dracula...
她就是Ilona
She is Ilona.
你绝不能再提
You must never again mention
Mina Murray长得像我妻子这件事
Mina Murray's resemblance to my wife.
钢镍合金
Nickel steel alloy.
困扰我们的问题得以解决了
The answer to our resonating casing problem.
唯一股东  帝国军火公司
Sole shareholder, empire munitions.
Shaw将军收受贿赂
General Shaw is taking bribes.
我不知道你还乐于
I didn't know you had such a remarkable penchant
摧毁无辜男人的一生
for ruining the lives of innocent men.
你又怎能确定
What makes you so sure
你自己不会遭此厄运？
that you are immune from the same fate?
她不是会计
She's not a bookkeeper.
是个演员
She's an actress.
我都按你的要求办了
I did everything you asked.
我促其进程
I refined the process.
你终将行于日下
You will finally be able to walk in sunlight.
你最好长话短说
Might I recommend keeping it short for once?
我们对血清时效一无所知
We have no idea how long the serum will last.
如果你和Grayson关系密切
If you are involved with Grayson
他又真是吸血鬼
and he proves to be a vampire,
你将面对的是勃然大怒的兄弟会
you will face the full wrath of the brotherhood.
女性有很多隐秘的方式传递爱慕
Women have many secret ways of expressing desire.
Mina可能对你有同样的感觉
Mina likely feels the same way about you.
你得离开了
You need to leave.
- 你找到了  - 德雷斯顿三联画
- You found it. - The Dresden triptych.
Grayson能源公司
成了 弄好了
There. Finished.
大家各就各位
Everyone to their stations.
Kowalski先生 开始吧
Mr. Kowalski, fire it up.
火力全开
Full power.
各就各位
Get to your stations!
你上一次吸血是什么时候?
When did you last feed?
钢镍合金啊
Nickel steel alloy.
如果连它也无法驯服这机器
If this doesn't tame the beast,
就没东西可以了
nothing will.
回答我  多久了
Answer me. How long has it been?
这不该是你所应关心的  教授
My habits are not your concern, professor.
你这是在玩火自焚
You're playing with fire.
我很清楚自己要什么
I'm well aware of my needs.
我被他们折磨四个多世纪了
I've been cursed with them for over four centuries.
- 你需要血！  - 我并不饿
- You need blood! - I'm not hungry.
先生们  我们准备好了
Gentlemen, we're ready.
Kowalski先生  全力以赴啊
Mr. Kowalski, by all means.
就是这样  先生们
That's it, gentlemen.
Kowalski先生
Mr. Kowalski,
带他们去最近的公馆畅饮
take these men to the nearest public house.
我请客
Drinks on me.
- 好的先生! - 玩的开心 小伙儿们
- Yes, sir! - And take it easy, boys.
我希望公众展示那天
I want this place shipshape
这里一切就绪
for our public demonstration,
随后日子里
and the day after that, well,
我会证明自己
I won't be worth a damn
而恶龙会将一无所有
and the Order Draco won't have a pot to piss in.
Harker
Harker.
Shaw将军是无辜的
General Shaw is innocent.
他从未收受贿赂推动战争
He never took bribes to promote war.
但你的线人…
But your informant...
她是个被收买了的演员
My informant was a paid actress.
真的吗
Really?
谁会这样做？
Who would do such a thing?
- 这骗局是精心设计的 - 嗯哼
- The hoax was elaborate. - Hm.
也需要谋划和资金
That takes planning and funds.
无论谁做的  他们坐享其成
Whoever did this, they sit to benefit from it
金钱利益亦或是…
financially or at...
是你
It was you.
别犯傻了
Don't be absurd.
我不是很明确地告诉过你
Was I not the one who told you explicitly
要放弃这桩生意的吗?
to drop the whole business?
是  但你知道我不会
Yes, after you knew that I couldn't.
不会那样做  你到底做了什么？
That I wouldn't.What have you done?
Harker  我们…只是做了必须做的
We, Harker, have done what was necessary.
一个值得尊敬的人名声被毁
An honorable man's reputation destroyed.
这有必要？
That was necessary?
一个为能源战争倒下的卒子罢了
Just another fallen soldier in the energy war.
前有古人  后还会有来者
Not the first. Not the last.
你让我成了同谋
You've made me accomplice to this.
我要揭发你
I'll expose you.
揭发我什么?
Expose what?
是你找到的那个会计
You were the one who sought out the bookkeeper.
是你把那些伪造的文件
You were the one who sent the forged documents
发给报社
to the newspapers.
不是我毁了他
I didn't destroy the man.
是你
You did.
那现在  我们能言归正传了吧？
Now, shall we return to the business at hand?
我计划举办一次关于共振器的展会
I'm planning a demonstration of my resonator.
我需要你给媒体发邀请函
I need you to send out invitations to the press.
有问题吗?
Will that be a problem?
没有
No.
这才是好小伙儿
There's a good lad.
Grayson无线磁能
展演会
都看了这垃圾了吧?
You've seen this rubbish?
你必须承认  他相当聪明
Well, you must admit. He's quite clever.
- 天啊  - 怎么了？
- Good God, man. - What?
难道你还对他倾慕?
Are you saying you admire the fellow?
不  当然不是
No. Certainly not.
我只是欣赏他玩的计谋
One just admires the game he plays.
他攻 我们就守
He thrusts, we parry.
Grayson使我们一直处于防御状态
Grayson keeps us on the defensive.
接下来该换他防守了
Then let's make him run for a change.
我们在苏格兰警局里的人是谁
Our man at Scotland Yard, Winthrop.
Morrow探长  先生
Chief Inspector Morrow, sir.
你打算怎么做?
What are you going to do?
做一些不太绅士的事
Something not befitting a gentleman.
- 噢  Winthrop - 是 先生
- Oh, and Winthrop. - Yes, sir.
也许是时候把小Harker带来了
Perhaps it's time we brought in Young Harker.
翻译: 小鱼  资本论
见习翻译：蜗小牛  句号
翻译 校对：幸福ing形式
德  古  拉
第一季 第七集
真 爱 字 幕 组
——— 出 品 ———
你在布达佩斯要小心
Now, you will be careful in Budapest?
你要需要
If you wish,
我可以给你雇个保镖
I can employ some bodyguards to protect you.
我更乐意依靠自己  先生
I'm perfectly capable of defending myself, sir.
很好
Good.
这任务我只放心你去做
I would not trust this task to anyone.
在我父亲的城堡被洗劫一空
After my father's castle was sacked,
数百年的
priceless heirlooms
家族珍宝遗失殆尽
that had been in my family for centuries were lost.
我对此没什么留恋
I would put a match to them all.
除了一样东西
All but one.
Renfield  把那画给我带回来
Renfield, bring that painting back to me.
把它带回去
Bring her home.
四个小时
Four hours.
我的技术目前只能做到这样
My skills can afford you no more than that yet.
真的吗  Abraham
Really, Abraham?
承认自己能力有限
How humble you are
你太谦虚了
to so readily admit your limitation.
不是你风格啊
Quite out of character.
是你的需求提升了  对吧
It is the improvement you demanded, no?
对现在来说已经足够了
It is enough for now.
你为什么不吸血了
Why do you abstain from blood?
Markham小姐的血治好了我
Miss Markham served to heal my burns.
在那后我还没吸血呢
But I have not fed since,
或许我从来都不该吸血
and perhaps I never shall.
你的血清改变了我
Your infusion has changed me.
我感觉…重生了
I feel...reborn.
再世为人
A man once more.
自欺欺人
You deceive yourself.
没有什么…可以治愈你的饥饿
There's no... cure for your hunger.
你永远都是它的奴隶
You will always be its servant.
我不做任何人的奴隶
I'm servant to no man.
Murray小姐
Miss Murray.
- 哦  - 今天早了五分钟
- Oh. - Five minutes early today.
Gyayson先生
Mr. Grayson.
我吓到你了？
Did I startle you?
没有  我只是
No. I was just...
你在哪儿干嘛
What in the world are you doing here?
跟其他人一样
Same as everyone else.
享受阳光
Sunshine.
难得的待遇
It's a rare treat.
我可以吗
May I?
要知道  在阳光明媚的日子里
You know, it should be a crime
不微笑可是犯罪哟
not to smile on so beautiful a day.
所以  你愁什么呢
So, what's troubling you?
如果你不想说  我
If you'd rather not say, I...
不  不  真的没事
No, no, it's quite all right.
我经常帮我爸爸在医院巡房
I was assisting my father on his rounds at hospital,
但我们吵架了
and we had an argument.
在皇家医院的生活单调无聊
Life at Bethlem can be relentlessly bleak.
日子也枯索无味
The days can be so monotonous.
要是这种单调的生活
What if that kind of tedium
影响他们的恢复怎么办？
hinders their recovery?
他们应该跳跳舞
They should dance.
什么
What?
跳舞  创造活力
Dance. Energy.
让血液跳动起来
Gets the blood pumping.
真是好主意
What an idea.
你怎么会这么想
How did you ever think of that?
我喜欢跳舞
I like to dance.
但我老爸不喜欢
Father does not.
这需要一些令人信服的说法儿
It might take some convincing.
哦  我相信你具有说服力
Oh, I'm sure you can be very persuasive.
而且倔强
And obstinate.
我的缺点之一
One of my many flaws.
你的缺点呢
And yours?
很久以前…
A long memory...
我会急躁
Impatience...
而且嫉妒
Envy.
你也会想要拥有
What could you possibly desire
不是你能随意得到的东西吗
that is not already yours for the taking?
我想你收到了我的花
I see you got my flowers.
我按了门铃  但是没人回应
I rang, but no one answered.
- Jenkins  - 你知道吗
- Jenkins? - You know,
我听到从餐具厅传来的声音
I heard some sounds coming from the pantry.
发现Jenkins先生正在看着你的厨子
I found Mr. Jenkins seeing to your cook.
看着她？
Seeing to her?
急切的看着她
Vigorously seeing to her.
恩
Hm.
你扎到手了
You pricked your finger.
嗯
Hm.
我们下楼看看吧
Shall we go downstairs and watch?
不要
No.
我们上楼吧
Let's go upstairs.
噢
Oh...
哦  大白天和你滚床单  这…
Oh, to have you here in broad daylight, it's...
有点颓废堕落
it's quite decadent.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我老公
It's my husband.
他经常在庄园里
He appears to have gotten involved with the nurse
跟照看他的护士纠缠不清
who tends to him at our country estate.
时有发生  无伤大雅
That happens. Harmless enough.
我先前也这样想  但是  额
Yes, that's what I thought at first, but, uh...
这老笨蛋居然声称自己爱上了她
silly old fool is claiming he's in love with her.
他真够厚颜无耻的
He's become quite brazen about it.
我该报复的   但是
I would reciprocate, of course, but...
但是对于他声誉的任何打击
But any damage inflicted upon his reputation
都可能会转嫁到你身上
would in turn be a strike against your own.
真是进退两难
It's a quandary.
告诉我
Tell me...
Alexander  如果你是我
What would you do in my position,
你会怎么办
Alexander?
我会找他的情人
I'd go after the object of his affection.
收拾她…就是伤了他
By wounding her... you wound him.
- 一场舞会  - 一场什么
- A dance. - A what?
我知道这不符合常规
I know it's unconventional.
这太荒唐了
That's an understatement.
但是爸爸
But father,
跳舞会鼓励社交
a dance would encourage socialization,
音乐有治愈的疗效
and music has such a power for healing.
医院的所有病患
The men and women of this hospital
住在单人间是有原因的
live in separate wards for good reason.
过去有过暴力事件
In the past there have been incidents of violence
- 不检点的行为  - 哦  上帝保佑
- and indecent behavior. - Oh, God forbid!
- Mina  - 爸爸
- Mina. - Father.
这些可怜人大多永远都不能回家
Most of these poor souls will never return home.
他们已经失去了自己简单快乐的生活
They have lost the simple pleasures of leading their own lives.
我们难道不能稍微让他们
Can we not give them one small reminder
回味下过往的生活吗
of the lives they've left behind?
医院财政可不会出一分钱
Not a penny may come from the hospital budget.
按指示向每个报社发送了邀请
Sent invitations to every newspaper as instructed.
太好了  这些是？
Excellent. And these are?
他们的拒绝信
Their refusals.
理由呢？
What reason do they give?
是你
You.
他们说你就是个卖万金油的
They say you're a charlatan peddling snake oil,
就如同P.T Barnum
like P.T. Barnum.
像P.T. Barnum
Like P.T. Barnum.
好 要是他们想看马戏表演
Well, if they want a circus,
爷给他们演一个便是
I'm gonna give 'em one.
绝对令他们难忘
One they won't soon forget.
Grayson无线磁电力
老少爷们都看过来！
Come one! Come all!
快来看壮观的电！
Come see the magnificent electricity!
汲取于天地之精华！
Drawn from the earth below and sky above!
您定会大开眼界！
You won't believe your eyes!
Harker 那好吧
Well, then, Harker.
现在我们已是伦敦的焦点
Now we have London's attention.
不久我们将为世界所瞩目
Very soon we'll have the world's.
Alexander 你病了吗？
Alexander, are you ill?
没
No.
想来是昨晚喝的有点高
Just had a little bit too much to drink last night.
也许真是岁月不饶人
Perhaps my age is catching up to me.
- 天  - 那么
- Goodness. - Well,
运气好的话在这能碰到
they should be there, with any luck.
女士们先生们各就各位
Come now, ladies and gentlemen.
现在即将拍卖的是德累斯顿三联画
The Dresden triptych now come to auction.
要竞得这样一件15世纪的大师之作
For the 15th century's masterpiece
我们从14万克朗起跳不算过吧？
I think we can go higher than 140,000 coronas, no?
是的  夫人
Yes, madam.
15万
150,000 coronas.
有出17万5的吗？
Do I have 175?
谢谢您了  夫人  非常感谢
There it is, madam. Thank you very much.
有出二十万的吗吗？
Do I have 200?
谢谢您了先生
It is yours, sir.
22.5万？
225?
谢夫人您的出价  25万有吗？
I can see you, madam. 250?
又是坐在后面的这位先生
Yes again, sir, in the back.
有出27万5的吗？
Do I have 275?
没有？那好
No? Very well, then.
25万   成交
Closing at 250,000 coronas.
- 女士们先生们…  - 100万
- Ladies and gentlemen... - 1 million.
先生 你在说什么？
Did you say, sir?
我出一百万克朗 用英镑支付
1 million corona. Payable in British sterling.
好的先生
Good lord.
我敢问下
Dare I ask for 1 million,
有出110万的吗？
100,000 coronas?
那就成交
Then sold.
德累斯顿三联画
Dresden triptych
100万克朗
for 1 million coronas.
这次换我惊到您了
Now it's my turn to surprise you,
Grayson先生
Mr. Grayson.
确实啊
And so you have.
我正在为明天的展示
I was preparing my speech
准备演讲呢
for the demonstration tomorrow night.
- Harker不在这 - 是啊  呃
- Harker isn't here. - No. Um...
我是过来跟您说两句的
I came to speak to you.
我？
Me?
好吧 要是是这个情况
Well, in that case,
我就得把演讲放放了
my speech can wait.
您身体不适吗？
Are you unwell?
您…你在出汗呢
You--You're perspiring.
我身体再好不过了
I've never been better.
我向你保证 无须担心
I assure you. No need for concern.
您盛大的展示
Everyone in London's
已经在伦敦妇孺皆知
been talking about your big night.
我很高兴设备成功修好了
I'm glad the repairs were successful.
前排给你留了座位
There's a seat reserved for you at the front.
好遗憾  我另有安排了
Unfortunately, I have another engagement.
- 嗯  - 你知道吗
- Hmm. - You see,
爸爸同意在医院开一场舞会了
father has consented to a dance at the hospital.
那真好
Brava.
- 你实在能说服别人啊  - 是啊
- Persuasive, indeed. - Yes.
我想 径直向您借留声机
And I wonder, would it be terribly forward
是否有几分冒昧？
if I asked to borrow your marvelous phonograph?
那不过是个小场合
It's quite a modest affair,
不过没有伴奏就不能称其为舞会了
but a dance isn't a dance without music,
- 不是吗？  - 我会让人给你送去
- is it? - I'll have it delivered.
你不必为音乐这类小事操心
You shan't want for music. Or anything.
谢谢
Thank you.
我将如何能补偿你的慷慨大度呢？
How shall I ever repay such kindness?
Murray小姐 给我点时间
Give me time, Miss Murray.
我确信我会想出一个的
I'm confident I'll think of something.
亲爱的 我敢肯定
My dear, I'm sure
你一定是误解了Mina的举动
you must have mistaken Mina's reaction.
不 你错了
No. You are wrong.
你当时不在那
You weren't there.
我知道究竟发生了什么
I know what I saw.
那究竟是怎么回事？
And what was that?
厌恶  - 不
Revulsion. - No.
你看到的不过是恐惧
What you saw was fear.
不 我了解她胜过我自己
No. You don't know her like I do.
是啊 也许我不知道
No, perhaps not,
可我确实了解她这个类型
but I know her type very well.
软弱的小东西
Timid little creatures.
对自己的欲望畏首畏尾
Afraid of their own desires.
看看我们俩…
See, you and I...
跟她完全不是一类
We're a different breed.
我们勇敢 我们诚实
We are brave. We are honest.
你的朋友 坦白说
Your friend's behavior has been cowardly,
懦弱到丑恶的地步
frankly monstrous.
的确丑恶 不是吗？
It was monstrous, wasn't it?
嗯
Mm-hmm.
谁知道她心肠歹毒？
Who knew she had such venom in her?
她实在伤透了我的心
Truly she's cut me to the very bone.
Mina是那么的聪明
Clever Mina.
她懂那么多
She knows so much.
却不懂痛苦为何物
She knows nothing of pain.
还不如我了解得透
Not as I do.
若她自己被爱人辜负
How would she feel to be let down
又会怎么想呢？
by the one she loves?
被Jonathan辜负？
By Jonathan?
这实在会是深刻的教训呢
Well, that would be a terrible lesson, indeed.
是啊 是啊 绝对的
Yes. Yes, it would.
你听说明晚要举办的盛会了吗？
This spectacle tomorrow evening, you've heard of it?
我当然听说了
Of course I have.
局子里一半的小伙子
Half the boys of the yard
都要请假去
have requested off to be there.
Morrow探长
Chief Inspector Morrow,
协会需要你的尽职尽责
the Order requires your services
谨言慎行
and your discretion.
谢谢你
Thank you.
一期实验算是顺利
Initial test holds steady.
一切都沿着正轨运行
All seems to be in order.
写完演讲稿了吗？
Have you written your speech yet?
Kowalski  这条链子锈了
Kowalski, this roller chain's covered in rust.
我没看出哪锈了
I don't see any rust.
你修就是！
Just fix it!
你看起来不太对劲
You're not looking well.
教授  若我是你
I would tread very carefully
就会懂得分寸
if I were you, professor.
今晚的复仇任务
This evening our revenge rests
可就全扛在你肩上了
on your shoulders,
可你这肩膀
yet you look too weak
现在连自己都撑不住
to shoulder your own garments!
你会复仇的
You will have your revenge.
摧毁他们之后我们都会
When we crush them, we both will.
但对我来说更好的是
But the greater measure of mine is to defy
把他们在我身上下的诅咒也毁掉
this blasted curse they've placed on my head.
我不会再杀人了
I will not kill.
不会再去吸血
I will not feed.、
我要做为一个人继续活下去
I will live as a man
要不然就去死
or not at all.
你还是个处女吧
You're a virgin, aren't you?
我看过你调情
I've seen you flirt.
毫无经验
You wear your inexperience
就像廉价的胭脂粉
like a cheap rouge.
你这么说太绝情了
Now you're just being cruel.
你看  所有少女
You know, all young ladies
把自己打扮得像只孔雀
preen like peacocks,
想变成最引人注目
thinking that the loudest
最闪亮的那个
and the brightest
这样才能吸引男人的目光
will draw the man's eye.
就连街头的妓女
But any streetwalker
也知道用淫笑拉拢客人
can simper and giggle.
我会教你
I will teach you
如何抓住Jonathan的心
how to haunt Jonathan's dreams.
一个女人的魅力
You see, a woman's power
不在于她的美貌和笑容
isn't in her beauty or her smile
而是她的内在
but in her mind,
对于你来说最有用的是
and the best application of yours
抓住Jonathan的五种感觉
will be in capturing Jonathan's five senses.
触觉
Touch.
你的指尖滑过他的肩膀
Your fingertips across his arm,
脸颊  和胸前
his chest, his cheek.
嗅觉
Scent.
夏天的记忆
Memories of summer
让他回忆起夏天
reminding him of the warm sun
温暖的阳光
on his naked skin.
听觉  你的笑声
Sound. Your laugh.
优雅轻盈
Light and gentle
如同水晶做的铃铛
like a crystal bell.
视觉
Sight.
徘徊的眼神
A look that lingers
似乎饱含承诺
and promises so much more.
最后
And finally...
什么
Yes?
继续
Go on.
味觉
Taste.
巧妙地使用这些
Wield these blades wisely,
亲爱的
my dear,
Jonathan很快就可以被拿下
and Jonathan will be an easy kill.
抱歉  吓到你了小姐
I am sorry to scare you, Miss,
今天不需要打扫
but no cleaning today, please.
是  对不起先生
Yes, sir. Beg your pardon, sir.
大家下午好
Good afternoon, sister.
我为舞会准备了些花
Just some flowers for the dance.
Lucy 这些真的没必要
Lucy, this is all very unnecessary.
我知道在婚礼上
I'm more than capable of choosing
要穿什么衣服
my own wedding garments.
我知道现在的小伙子
I know the chaps
都会带乳色的手套
are all wearing ivory wedding gloves now,
但巴黎的人都带薰衣草色
but they're back to lavender in Paris.
你考虑的很周到
You seem well, considering.
怎么周到了
Considering what?
前两天晚上
The other night.
Mina告诉我你很沮丧的原因
Mina told me why you were so upset.
Alistair
Alistair.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
当然
Oh, yes. Of course.
这样最好
It's for the best.
他并不是我的菜
He wasn't exactly my type.
嗯
Hm.
她还说了什么吗
Did she say anything else?
没 怎么
No. Why?
哦不 可怜的伙计
Oh, no, no, no. You poor lamb.
让我来吧
Allow me.
我来
I insist.
做得好
Well done.
新鲜的馅饼
Pies fresh today!
早上新鲜的馅饼
Fresh this morning.
刚从烤炉出来的
Right out of the oven.
我可以吗
Do you mind if I...
没关系 自便吧
No. Just go ahead. Go on.
新鲜的馅饼  新鲜的馅饼
Fresh pies, fresh pies,
今天新鲜的馅饼
fresh today!
- 谢谢  - 不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
让我来
Allow me.
我们又回到远点了
Start at the beginning.
有问题吗
Any trouble?
没什么我控制不了的
Nothing I couldn't handle.
你最爱的是什么
So who do you love most,
Alexander Grayson
Alexander Grayson?
Mina Murray
Mina Murray.
我会尽快回来
I'll be back shortly.
Jonathan Harker 先生
Mr. Jonathan Harker?
- 什么 - 我代表
- Yes? - Come on behalf
Browning先生
of Mr. Browning...
他现在要跟你谈谈
He'd like a word with you at once.
给我写信就可以了
Well, a letter would have sufficed.
是的 我只是去参加
As it is, I'm just on my way...
展示会  他知道
Demonstration. Yes. He's aware.
只要一会就好 可以吗
He asked but a moment, please?
如果我拒绝呢
And if I refuse?
这会使这件事变得有点点麻烦 先生
Make the task at hand a great deal messier, sir.
请坐  Harker先生
Please remain seated, Mr. Harker,
要不然我们就要束缚你了
or we shall be forced to restrain you.
Browning先生
Mr. Browning.
是我
Correct.
我在这
I am here.
虽然 你断言是我
Although, if you ever allege that I was,
但我有四个可靠的证人
I have four unimpeachable witnesses
他们会一口咬定我现在
who will testify under oath that I am at present
在Gresham俱乐部用晚餐
dining at the Gresham Club.
这什么意思  为什么我在这
What is this about? Why am I here?
我只是想把你介绍给我同事认识
I merely wish to present you to my colleagues,
他们目前还不能暴露身份
who shall remain anonymous for the time being.
- 你的同事  - 是的
- Your colleagues? - Ah, yes.
欢迎 Harker先生
Welcome, Mr. Harker,
来到龙之会
to the Order of the Dragon.
花园里的雏菊
And with daisies from the garden.
不用花一分钱
Not a single penny was spent.
这不能与Chatsworth庄园舞厅比
It might not be the ballroom at Chatsworth
但它本该如此
but it should do.
你真是太令人钦佩了 亲爱的
Admirably resourceful, my dear.
Grayson先生的留声机也会摆在这
And Mr. Grayson's phonograph should be here, too.
嗯
Ah.
你听到了吗
Do you hear that?
受你邀请 Murray小姐
As you requested, Miss Murray.
你的音乐
Your music.
Murray医生
Dr. Murray.
我能邀请您跳支舞吗  女士
May I trouble you for this dance, my lady?
这个房间里所有的人
Every man in this room
都已发过誓
has sworn an oath
他会因为上帝的旨意而牺牲自己
that he will give up his life in order to serve God's word.
你可以做到吗  Harker先生
Are you such a man, Mr. Harker?
愿与我们同舟共济
Are you one of us?
作出牺牲吗？
Would you make that sacrifice?
面对威胁  是的  坚定不移
In the face of a threat? Yes. Without hesitation.
至此之刻  威胁亦存
Even as we speak, such a threat exists.
以前有一个异教徒
An ancient enemy...
现在我们知道此人是奥斯曼人
The heathens now known as the Ottomans.
奥斯曼帝国坐拥油海
The Ottomans sit on a sea of oil.
如果我们不能为英国等西方国家
If we do not secure those reserves for England
得到那些石油资源
and the West then soon,
那么很快  原油运输会被中断
very soon, with the turn of the spigot,
他们有能力
they will have the power
使整个西部的工业停滞
to shut down Western industry,
当我们手无缚鸡之力的时候
and when we are defenseless
他们会群起叛变摧毁我们
their hordes will rise up and crush us.
但是
But...
我能说句吗？
If I may?
请说
Please.
如果如你所言
If what you say is true,
那么Grayson能源计划
then Mr. Grayson's energy scheme
终会夺走奥斯曼人最厉害的武器
will utterly strip the Ottomans of their greatest weapon.
有了电磁力  我们就不需要石油了
With geomagnetic power, we'll have no need for oil.
Grayson的技术就完全没有用武之地了
Grayson's technology is a dead end.
只要引起骚乱  事态发展下去
A distraction, and if it continues,
结果必然一败涂地
one that may prove deadly.
我们不能让一个满嘴胡说
We cannot afford to be led astray
时刻想填满自己腰包的人
by a latter-day pied piper whose interests begin
把我们带偏了
and end with lining his own pockets.
- 我们应该去阻止他  - 但是
- It is our duty to stop him. - But...
我们需要你的协助
We need your help.
你们让我做叛徒吗
You'd have me play Judas?
是  去搬倒这个伪救世主
To bring down a false messiah, yes,
作为回报
and in return,
你得到的权力和人脉
power and connections that would ensure
可助你和Murray小姐坐享美好未来
the brightest of futures for you and Miss Murray.
加入我们吧   Harker先生
Join us, Mr. Harker.
协助我们  赢得这神圣的一战
Help us to win this Holy War once and for all.
你不会现在就要走了吧
You're not leaving already.
抱歉  我要去展会
Forgive me. The demonstration.
告诉Harker  那里见
Tell Harker I'll see him there.
但一个小时后展会才开始
But it doesn't start for another hour,
而且Jonathan还没来  虽说他答应会来
and Jonathan's not here, although he promised.
我相信你很轻松
I'm sure you'll have no
就能再找到一个舞伴
trouble finding another partner to dance with.
近在眼前嘛
I already have.
Murray小姐  人们会议论你的？
Miss Murray, what would people say?
有人看到吗？
What people?
跟我跳支舞吧
Dance with me.
- 先生  这边走  - 我们到了
- There you go, sir. - Here we are.
这个是给您的
And one for you.
这是您的  先生  还有夫人您的
There's one for you, sir, and you, ma'am.
多谢  这个给您  先生
Thank you very much. And one for you, sir.
- 他在哪儿？  - 我想他们给我的衣服
- Where is he? - I think they gave me
- 不合身  - 他在哪儿？
- the wrong one. - Where is he?
我从来没见他们这么开心  多亏了您
I've never seen them so happy, and all because of you.
谢你就够了
They only have you to thank for it.
有你照拂  花儿都会开的格外美
Why, any flower would blossom under your care.
您抬举我了
You flatter me.
这让你不好意思了吗
Does that make you uncomfortable?
是的
Yes.
那我是不是该闭嘴了
Should I stop?
不
No.
你的手
Your hands.
您的手在发抖
Your hands are trembling.
抱歉
Forgive me.
怎么了？
What's happening?
没什么  才是问题
Nothing. That's the problem.
你的老板临阵脱逃了
Your boss is a no-show.
女士们  先生们  我们有理由相信
Ladies and gentlemen, we have reason to believe
这个机器会威胁到公共安全
that this machine is a threat to public safety,
所以请大家从出口
so if you'll all please move towards the exit
有秩序地离场
in an orderly fashion.
谢谢
Thank you.
女士们  先生们  撤离此处
Ladies and gentlemen, move along.
快点  女士们  先生们
Quick as you can, ladies and gents.
关了机器  把它封起来
Shut it down! Pack it all up.
我要没收这些东西
I want all this confiscated.
这是私人财产！  你无权干涉！
This is private property! You have no right!
这机器放这里没几天
Next door there are over a hundred souls sick as dogs
附近就有一百多人病得不轻
not days after this infernal machine was constructed.
绝不可能！
That's impossible!
这机器绝无健康隐患
This poses absolutely no health risks!
去和那个妈妈解释吧
Tell that to the mum with the baby in her arms
孩子还在她怀里吐着血呢
who's spittin' up blood.
很显然  你是拿了别人的钱
Clearly you're not above being paid for your services,
无论谁给的  我给你双倍价格
so how much to double whoever's paid you off?
放开你的脏手！
Get your damn hands off her!
滚！
Get out!
走开！
Go away!
快走！  快！
Come on! Come on.
往前走  快  快
Come along! Move. Move.
快
Come on.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我知道我该陪你的
I know I should have been here.
带我回家
Take me home.
Paul
Paul.
Paul！
Paul!
你应该收下那些钱
You should have taken the money.
啊！
Aah!
小“酌”一口去了？
Off for a little lip, were we?
跟你相比  这算得了什么
My savagery pales in comparison to yours.
你不应把我拉回那个
You won't drag me back into this world
唾弃我的世界
that had forsaken me.
是你  拿血清忽悠我
You, who cheated me with the vaccine
让我体验那种
that gives me but the taste of the life
绝无可能过上的生活的滋味
I can never have.
是你  给了我希望
You, who gave me hope.
你比我更像怪物
You're more of a monster than I am,
有朝一日
and someday...
我会为此杀了你
I will kill you for it.